consumerlifestylemag.com 2011-08-06

# Lifestyle Headlines.com | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (Policy) discloses the practices of Lifestyle Headlines concerning personal information we obtain about you. By using Lifestyle Headlines, in any way accessing Lifestyle Headlines, or using other services of Lifestyle Headlines (collectively the Services), you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

This Policy notifies you of: (a) what personal information of yours is collected when you access Lifestyle Headlines and/or use the Services; (b) how the information is collected; (c) how the information is used and shared; (d) our efforts to maintain the security of Sensitive Information; and (e) other details concerning your personal information and our policies.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Lifestyle Headlines does not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

**Collection and Use of Information**

Information collected by Lifestyle Headlines is stored in a single, secure database, accessible only by Lifestyle Headlines. We collect information from our paying members or other persons who use, attempt to use, or access Lifestyle Headlines or the Services (users) at several different points and from different sources, all or some of which may apply to you:

**Registration**

When you sign up as a customer or potential customer, we ask for, and you are required to give, your email address. Once you register with us, you are not anonymous to us.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser.

**Log Files**

LifestyleHeadlines automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your Web browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We use IP addresses and cookies to analyze trends, administer the site, track members and users movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to your personal information.

**Use of Information**

Information we collect is generally used for the following purposes:  
To build features that will make the services available on our site easier to use. This includes faster search requests, better member support and timely notice of new services and special offers.  
To improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our sites content, layout, and services. These uses improve our Services and better tailor them to meet your needs.  
To resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. At times, we may look across multiple members or users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify members using multiple Member Ids or aliases.

**Promotions**

We send all new members a welcoming email. Active members and former members may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

**Security**

LifestyleHeadlines takes every precaution to protect our users and members Sensitive Information, both online and offline. Your Sensitive Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. Sensitive Information is encrypted and is protected online with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL.  
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email LifestyleHeadlines Contact Us.

**Notification of Adjustment**

If we decide to change our Policy, we will post these changes on our Homepage or provide other notification of our revised Policy so our users and members are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we disclose it.
